{
	"data": [
        {
            "question": "A: Who does this red jumper belong to?\nB: It ___ to Sam. He was wearing a red jumper this morning.",
            "a": "might belong",
            "b": "can belong",
            "c": "couldn't belong",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "24",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Anna ___ Daniel your phone number. She doesn't know him.",
            "a": "couldn't have given",
            "b": "may not have given",
            "c": "might not have given",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "24",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ___ be late for the train. I don't want to miss it.",
            "a": "needn't",
            "b": "mustn't",
            "c": "don't have to",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "24",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "We booked a table in the restaurant because we thought it would be full. But when we got there, it was almost empty. We ___ a table at all.",
            "a": "mustn't have booked",
            "b": "needn't have booked",
            "c": "can't have booked",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "24",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I'm so happy, I ___!",
            "a": "could cry",
            "b": "can cry",
            "c": "must cry",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "24",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why didn't you tell me that you wanted a sandwich? I ___ one for you when I made mine.",
            "a": "can't have made",
            "b": "could have made",
            "c": "could make",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "24",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "It's surprising that this restaurant _________ be so successful. The food isn't very good.",
            "a": "might",
            "b": "should",
            "c": "would",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "24",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you ___ feel unwell after taking these tablets, contact your doctor immediately.",
            "a": "might",
            "b": "could",
            "c": "should",
            "answer": "3",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "24",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jack _________ in that team. It's for boys aged 15 to 18, and he's 20. We must tell him when the match finishes.",
            "a": "couldn't be playing",
            "b": "shouldn't be playing",
            "c": "needn't play",
            "answer": "2",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "24",
            "type": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tom _________ the CDs from the shop. That was a bad thing to do.",
            "a": "shouldn't have stolen",
            "b": "mustn't have stolen",
            "c": "shouldn't be stealing",
            "answer": "1",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "45",
            "subcategorylv2": "24",
            "type": "2"
        }
    ]
}